Stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
The paint within brings
out a map of your own.
To the left and the right,
all we saw stormy nights.
All the rough winds and
waves coming day after day.
And the values we had
were about to collapse.
Oh, just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see?
Is beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand,
cut through the wind and make A stand,
don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way,
the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and tone,
we'll go where we all want to go.
The page within brings colors of our own.
Hey!
What the heck are you doing?
You've got a flaw!
Yes, uh, that I did.
But...
My body will not heed my call!
Please, you must consider how large I am.
Merely lifting my head
will put me so high up.
That's kind of the point.
You're all grown up and you're
still scared of heights?
Mind your tongue.
I am a samurai.
Warriors such as I fear nothing.
Then stop whining and
start flying. I will.
Just give me a moment.
I'll do it later.
Why did you bother getting big if
you're still going to be a coward?
Just fly already.
Will you stop pushing me?
You are not helping!
We don't have time to argue!
I've been gone long enough!
Kaido could be killing
our friends right now!
I know that!
But my heart is unprepared!
Stop making excuses!
Not the eyelids! Please!
Shut your mouth!
We're taking down Kaido and
we're doing it together, okay?!
Mirror Mountain A
clever
defense I have a job to do
Luffy, we'll defeat you!
I just have to survive till he comes back!
Hallowed Glacier Splash!
you're a part of one and now you're
challenging me as if you're its hero
Yamato, you're an ogre, just like me.
You'll always be my child, and
you'll always have my blood!
Everything else is just a lie!
Shut your mouth!
You're trying to take on something
that can never belong to you,
But the samurai don't see you as an ally.
No matter what you do,
you won't bring their
approvals away in a tribe.
That's not the point.
You don't know how I feel.
You don't know a damn thing about me!
You've lived your whole
miserable life on this island.
And you've spent it all alone,
scuttering about in the ceilings like a
cockroach without a friend to your knee.
You think I don't have friends?
Well, you're wrong!
I made a friend who gave me hope.
Ethaneth, he's gone now.
Dead and lost, just like those
samurai you grew close to years ago.
Funny how everyone who's ever
been kind to you ends up dead.
No wonder it's so cold,
it's snowing, and now I'm starving again.
I'm so hungry.
I know you're there, ogre princess.
You don't need to run away.
I bet you're hungry, aren't you?
Here you go.
Take it before someone notices.
I can't stay here.
Thank you so much.
I appreciate it.
How?
Oh, God.
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
You saved me.
No problem.
Hang in there.
Hey, why did the commander
execute him all of a sudden?
He was delivering food to the
ogre princess and he got caught.
He even brought her a blanket
because the weather's been so cold.
Oh, what a nice guy.
So the princess is still on the run, huh?
Saying she wants to be Odin?
They didn't just die.
You killed them yourself.
I was trying to educate my
child, and they got in the way.
It's what they deserved.
You still haven't learned your lesson now.
Now, what'll it take?
I'm the only thing you have in this world.
You think those people from the
land of Wano are your friends?
But they don't give a damn about you!
They're just a convenience to them!
They'll come to fear you in the end.
You must rule people by force!
Because you're an ogre's child!
Humans will never come to
accept someone like you!
You're the same as me.
That is your fate.
Do you hear me?
Ghost of God!
I'm flying!
Hooray, you got this, Momo!
Keep moving! Don't look back!
That is my intent!
Let's go!
All the way to Onigashima!
Forward! Forward!
The dragon's true are fast!
If he can keep this,
he'll be there in no time!
We're getting off course! We gotta turn!
Momo, move to the left! Hurry!
Yes, left.
And left is this way.
Yeah! One minute!
All right, finally made it.
Don't see anyone yet.
I saw someone fighting way up top.
That's gotta be Kaido.
Let's try to aim for
the roof! The roof? Yes!
I shall take you there post-haste! No!
Now you're way too high!
You gotta go back down!
Right! Down I go!
No! Stop!
Now you're turning the wrong way!
What is your deal?
Are you flying with your
eyes closed or what?
Of course I am!
I'd be terrified if I could see!
What?!
Turn around!
You're flying the wrong way!
Three-sword style.
What is that?
A dragon?!
Commander Kino's here!
I don't think that's him!
Who the hell is that?!
Luffy!
Oh, oh no!
Slow down! Luffy!
He's okay!
Luffy!
I wish you're low-y!
Momo, stop!
Where are you going?
I know!
Why the hell are you pink?
Is that Straw Hat?
Hey, go away!
What the hell is going on here?
That's enough! Stop it!
Just open your eyes, Momo! No!
I fear I can't!
I think I got some debris stuck in them!
That's what you get for
crashing into everything!
Do something, Luffy! Help me!
Help yourself!
Show some guts and look ahead!
Stop! Stop!
This is their castle!
Third floor!
Commander Kinda was running wild in here!
No!
That's not the commander!
It can't be!
What do you mean?
You're saying there's
a second giant dragon?
There's gotta be! It's pink!
Chase it down and find
out who it is! Hooray!
It sure is noisy down there, huh?
It's Linlin, probably.
I'm gonna make that hag
pay for all the repairs.
I can't rest yet.
My job's not done!
divine swiftness all right there
he is we made it did we I...
I see.
We're up terribly high.
I'll find some place to land quickly.
Look there, on top of the roof.
Aim straight for Kaido!
Aim for Kaido.
Fourth gear!
Man!
Come back!
Define!
What's that?
White Serpent!
Jack Calderon!
The mehaw!
Nooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
I'm going to kill you!
The hell?
I'm so glad you're safe.
I've been waiting!
I don't believe we've met, unless...
Straw Hat...
How the hell are you still alive?
I still have work left to do.
I can't die till I become
king of the pirates!
Who are you? Dragon?
You better not be the one who
saved Straw Hat from death!
My name is Kozuki Momonosuke.
I am the man who will become
the land of Wano Shogun.
This feeling? Who's been? Huh?
Enjoying yourself Otago ?
Where are you going ?
Otama ?
This battle is far too dangerous
for a young girl like you.
Get back here right now!
I'm sorry, Master, but no!
I have to go and help everybody!
There's no need to worry, sir!
We will do everything within
our power to keep Otama safe.
I promise you.
Otama!
Please, let her be safe.
There's no way to know.
All I can do is wait.
We've just sighted a mysterious dragon.
It's currently on the rooftop,
alongside young master Yamato.
So it's Yamato who was
holding off the commander?
I can't believe what I'm seeing!
The two dragons are picking off!
The enemy was hiding in their cook car!
A pink dragon and an azure
dragon staring each other down.
What does this mean?
And there's someone on the dragon's back.
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
The pink dragon's identity is a mystery.
But I have no doubt, it is a deadly enemy.
Now that I look closer,
you're a dragon, aren't you?
Like my father.
I wish I could turn into
a monster like he does.
At least I'd be of some use to my friends.
Momonosuke!
What a surprise.
You grew up fast, brat.
Unfortunately for you, this world
isn't big enough for two giant dragons.
He's about to breathe fire, okay?
Now you'll breathe something, too.
What do you mean, breathe something?
Let us try!
Do it like Kaido!
You act like it's normal
for people to breathe fire!
Yes, please!
No, stop!
I'm not here to fight!
I'm peaceful!
Hey, Momo!
I need you to bite Kaido!
Bite him!
Now, third gear!
Wait, Luffy!
I can't do that!
You're asking too much!
Time to show him what we can do!
Gum-tum elephant guy!
Hey, Momo!
I need you to bite Kaido!
I can't!
Don't worry, I'll make
certain both of you escape.
Just hold on.
I know what to do.
Mother, no!
What?
No, no, no, no!
Your father was a fool of a lord.
Now tell me your name, dammit!
Spineless brat!
I'm hurt!
I don't!
What the hell are you doing?
Stay out of this!
You'll pay for what you did to
the land of Wano and its people!
If it weren't for you,
father would be here.
Mother would be here!
I said stay out of this,
you pathetic little brat!
Momonosuke, get out of there!
Blast me!
You did it, Momo!
Wait, what?
Did he just call him Momo?
That pink dragon is Lord Momonosuke?
Hey, how's that possible?
Our Shogun is doing Wano proud!
Now you know you have
the power to hurt Kaido!
Dragons bring thunderclouds, and
now there are two dragons here.
Your precious moon is gone,
and not a moment too soon.
If I had taken even one more attack, I
would be kneeling in defeat right now.
But the power your Su-Long transformation
grants you is a double-edged sword.
It's left you with no
more strength to fight.
Oh no, his power went away!
We shall come to your reign at once!
You have to wait your time!
The moon didn't betray you.
I just got lickety lucky, that's all.
You had a good run, but now it's
lickety lights out for you, boss cat.
Master!
Hey, Momo!
You know who you just took a bite out of?
An emperor of the sea!
Is there anything left in the
world that can scare you now?
No.
There isn't!
So fly!
With your eyes open this time!
I shall!
Your job...
is to stop Onigashima!
As for Kaido, I got this!
Hear that?
You're done for!
Wolfie's back!
Give him the old war, my boy!
Now this is gonna be...
Super!
You're a real riot, Straw Hat.
He sure likes to talk, Vic.
What's he been doing all this time?
Loopy!
And Momo, too!
Should have known.
He always keeps his word.
That's our Loopy for you.
Go, Vic Root!
You guys.
See you soon, Luffy.
Looks like it's finally time.
Yeah.
Let's get started.
Do you think you have even a
single chance of defeating me?
As long as I'm still alive,
I have infinite chances.
Aaaaaah!
Just like in the journal, Odin wrote about
this when Roger and Whitebeard clashed.
He said the heavens split open.
I have something to report.
The clouds have split.
I've heard enough from you, Karoo.
Ha!
Would you look at that?
Luck sees me back on my side.
I bet you're having a ball
up there, aren't you, Kaido?
Well, boys...
We can't let our friends
show us up, right?
Odin, one sword style!
Divine Frenzy!
Ah!
I'm taking that!
I won't tear you apart, you burglow!
K-9 Cleaver!
Pedro, I wish I could share I'll
share one last drink with you, Karoo,
under this beautiful moon.
That was amazing, Master!
Oh, Carrot!
You two are great!
I'm so glad you're okay!
That was a fine performance, Master!
Thanks!
You Karoo did what none of us could!
Pedro is a thing!
I would be proud!
Careful, everyone!
The moon's still out.
Yugara don't want to turn Sulong.
I wonder what made the clouds clear.
Having some crazy weather
tonight, that's for sure.
Now you know the rage of the meek people.
How can this be?
They took down Jack!
If they can stand up to a lead performer,
who knows what else they're capable of?
No matter.
After all, it's none of my concern now.